nga.net 2017-04-16

# Privacy Statement | Acendre

### Introduction

Acendre Pty Ltd (ACN 079 099 282) (“Acendre”) respects and upholds your rights under the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Privacy Act”). This Privacy Policy for Acendre lets you know what personal information of yours we hold, what we do with it, who we will disclose it to and how you can access the personal information we hold about you. You can also find out here how to change inaccurate personal information and how to opt out of receiving communications from us.

### What personal information about you does Acendre collect and hold?

Acendre does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide us with such information by submitting an online application to us or make an email enquiry. In relation to an online application, the information we collect will include any personal and sensitive information you provide to us to assess and process your application. In relation to email inquiries, this information will include your name, email address, address, employment or company details and any other information you provide to us in your inquiry.

If you decide to complete an online application form, the information you enter into the online form will only be collected by us if you submit your online application.

### How does Acendre collect and hold your personal information?

Where possible, Acendre will generally collect your personal information directly from you. Acendre also collects personal information from its clients in the course of providing services to them. We may also collect personal information from our website, in promotional activities such as promotional events and competitions, from other directly related companies and, where you have provided your consent, from the organisers of events that we sponsor.

### What does Acendre do with your personal information?

We will only use and disclose your personal information for the purposes which you provide it. In relation to inquiries you submit to us, we will use the information for the purposes of responding to your inquiry. In respect of online applications submitted to us, we will use this information to assess and process your application. In respect of personal information provided to us by our clients, we will use this information for the purpose of operating and maintaining our clients’ accounts, managing our services and fulfilling our legal and contractual obligations. ****

### Who will Acendre disclose your personal information to?

Acendre may disclose your personal information to Acendre staff involved in processing your application or inquiry as well as referees and other third parties who may be required to assist us in processing your application. We may also disclose your personal information to advisors, consultants and contractors we ordinarily engage for the above purposes (such as lawyers, accountants and IT service providers). Due to the sensitive nature of some of the information that is gathered on behalf of our clients, we may also require applicants to undertake security and background clearance checks. Where this is necessary we will obtain your prior consent.

We may disclose your personal information to third party service providers overseas who are not subject to similar laws to the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). However, where your personal information is disclosed to an overseas recipient, we will also take adequate measures to ensure that the personal information is handled by the overseas recipient in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and our instructions for the purposes described above. By providing Acendre with your personal information, you consent to this disclosure of your personal information.

### Openness

You may request access to personal information (including your credit information) we hold about you by contacting the Privacy Officer at the address below. Where we hold information that you are entitled to access, we will endeavour to provide you with a suitable range of choices as to how access is provided (eg emailing or mailing it to you). A fee may be charged to cover the cost of retrieval.

If at any time you believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, then you may request amendment of it and we will either amend the information or make a record of your comment, as we think appropriate.

### Marketing

Where we have obtained your consent to do so, or in circumstances where you would reasonably expect that your personal information would be used or disclosed for this purpose, we may contact you from time to time with marketing material about our other products or services. At any time, you may opt out of receiving this material at any time by contacting us by email to Marketing@Acendre. Your consent to receiving this information will remain current until you advise us otherwise. 

### Questions and complaints

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or believe that we have at any time failed to keep one of our commitments to you to handle your personal information in the manner required by the Privacy Act, then we ask that you contact us immediately using the following contact details [privacy@acendre.net.](mailto:privacy@acendre.net)

We will respond and advise whether we agree with your complaint or not. If we do not agree, we will provide reasons. If we do agree, we will advise what (if any) action we consider it appropriate to take in response. If you are still not satisfied after having contacted us and given us a reasonable time to respond, then we suggest that you contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (AIOC) by:

Phone: 1300 363 992 (local call cost, but calls from mobile and pay phones may incur higher charges).

**If calling from overseas** (including Norfolk Island): +61 2 9284 9749  
**TTY: 1800 620 241** (this number is dedicated to the hearing impaired only, no voice calls)

**TIS: Translating and Interpreting Service** : 131 450 (If you don’t speak English or English is your second language and you need assistance and ask for the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner)

Post: GPO Box 2999 Canberra ACT 2601  
Fax: +61 2 9284 9666  
Email: [enquiries@oaic.gov.au](mailto:enquiries@oaic.gov.au) ****

### Acendre Website

When visiting Acendre’s web site, the site server makes a record of the visit and logs the following information for statistical and administrative purposes: ****

  * The user’s server address – to consider the users who use the site regularly and tailor the site to their interests and requirements;
  * The date and time of the visit to the site – this is important for identifying the website’s busy times and ensuring maintenance on the site is conducted outside these periods;
  * Pages accessed and documents downloaded – this indicates to Acendre which pages or documents are most important to users and also helps identify important information that may be difficult to find;
  * Duration of the visit – this indicates to us how interesting and informative the Acendre site is to candidates; the type of browser used – this is important for browser specific coding
  * In order to optimise the Acendre  web site and better understand it’s usage, we collect the visiting domain name or IP address, Computer Operating System, Browser Type and Screen Resolution

### Retention and destruction of Personal Information

Acendre will retain your personal information after your relationship with us expires. However, should you wish for the information to be destroyed, you can do so by contacting our Privacy Officer. In this case your Personal Information will continue to be protected in accordance with this Policy. If we destroy Personal Information we will do so by taking reasonable steps and using up-to-date techniques and processes.

### Security of Information

Acendre will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our website and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorised access, use, modification, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

However, you should keep in mind that the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this website may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

To view our secure SSL site please visit:  

### Miscellaneous

In this policy “personal information” has the same meaning as under the Privacy Act.

This policy is effective from 12 March 2014. We may change this policy from time to time. Although we intend to observe this Privacy Policy at all times, it is not legally binding on Acendre in any way. From time to time we may regard it as necessary or desirable to act outside the policy. Acendre may do so, subject only to any other applicable contractual rights you have and any statutory rights you have under the Privacy Act or other applicable legislation.

The information on the Acendre website is intended as a general reference. Acendre will make every reasonable effort to maintain current and accurate information. The information and data on the Acendre web site is subject to change without notice. Users should carefully evaluate the accuracy, currency, completeness and relevance of this information for their purposes before relying on the material in any important matter.

### Acendre

  * Accept no liability for any use of or reliance placed on the said information and data;
  * Make no representations, either expressed or implied, as to the suitability of the said information and data for any particular purpose; and
  * Make no warranties that the said information and data are free of infection by computer viruses or other contamination.

Links to other sites are provided for readers’ convenience. Acendre does not accept responsibility for information on any web site beyond our own. In some cases the material may incorporate or summarise views, standards or recommendations of third parties. Such material is assembled in good faith, but does not necessarily reflect the considered views of Acendre, or indicate a commitment to a particular course of action.

To link your website to any part of the Acendre web site you can request permission by emailing us at [marketing@acendre.net.](mailto:marketing@acendre.net)
